Araceli Garcia

5770 Dream Fulfilled Rd, Las Vegas NV 89122 Contact: (805) 769-7043, arachelly23@gmail.com

OUALIFICATIONS/ SUMMARY

Strong leader who is energetic, outgoing, goal oriented, and has a drive for knowledge. Self-motivated and currently taking online classes on Lynda.com to achieve certificates on new skill sets and expand my knowledge in a never ending pursuit for development. Current student in Kenzie Academy for Software Engineering to be experienced in front-end and back-end web development, projected graduation is October 27. Proficient in Microsoft Office to collect data and run reports for a small and large industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amazon AR Sortable Facility— *Picker/ICQA/Learning Ambassador/Process Guide/Process Assistant* June 2019-Present

6001 E Tropical Pkwy Las Vegas, NV 89115- 2001 Commerce Pkwy Franklin, IN 46131

- ♦ Was a devoted Learning Ambassador that developed exceptional associates through retrains and improved productivity by an average of 7%.
 - ◆ High Frequency Coach that engaged with bottom performers in quality, performance, and time off task during Amazon's busiest time of the year.
 - ♦ Learned ASL (American Sign Language) to gain a better connection with Amazon's hearing-impaired associates while increasing their potential for leadership.
 - ◆ Supported the learning department with on-boarding and ensuring all associates follow our CDC safety rules during Covid-19.
 - ♦ Volunteered at an Amazon Fresh warehouse during Covid-19 to help with the overhaul in customer orders.
 - ♦ Vendor Flex Process Assistant that assists managers in running a department and supervising staff to ensure excellent work quality. Assisted with productivity throughout the department, filing reports and problem solving any issues that could delay customer orders.
 - ◆ As a Vendor Flex Process Assistant I ensure that our productivity was being met by a specific time for our drivers to ensure that our customers are able to receive their packages on the time they were promised
 - ♦ Have experience in ICQA, Pick, Pack, Dock, Returns, Problem Solve and Decant. ♦ Worked at the following sites: LAS7, LAS2, IND9, IND2, VUBB and VUH2.
 - ♦ Helped launch two Amazon Sites: one in Bakersfield, CA and Tucson, AZ.

Sitel- E-commerce Agent October 2018- May 2019 420 E Pilot Rd Las Vegas, NV 89119

◆ Effective communicator to de-escalate matters with members on displeased orders or experience. ◆ Helped Costco members with their online orders, which included returns, buying online items, tracking orders, and finding information on specific items.

Domino's – *Closing Manager and Insider* August 2015- June 2018 2138 Spring St Paso Robles, CA 93446-1007 S Guadalupe St Seguin, TX 78155

- Customer centric through answering phones, taking orders, and resolving concerns or complaints.
- ♦ Responsible for depositing money, sending out tips, and maintaining inventory records when closing the store.
- ♦ Organized associates and route driver's schedules to ensure shifts were filled efficiently and workers were covered when vacation was submitted.

EDUCATION/ HOBBIES

- ♦ Paso Robles High School Diploma
- ♦ Kenzie Academy Software Engineering Current
- ♦ Created a Club, Make A Difference 2015-2018
- ♦ Interned at Twin Cities Hospital 2017-2018
- ♦ Volunteered at Twin Cities 2015-2016
- ♦ Volunteered for People Housing Association 2017-2018